Guide to the Campus Telephone Directory Collection, 1930-2009
Duke University. University Archives
Campus Telephone Directory collection 1930-2009
Duke University. University Archives
Duke University
9.5 linear feet Extent: 200 Items
This collection contains Duke University campus telephone directories.
UA.01.11.0089
Language: Material in English.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Campus Telephone Directory Collection were received by the University Archives as a transfer.
Collection Overview
This collection contains Duke University campus telephone directories.
Detailed Description of Collection
- Container List, 1930-2009, (19 boxes)
  - 1930-1964 (not inclusive) (Box 1.1)
  - 1966-1974/1975 (Box 1.2)
  - 1974/1975-1980/1981 (Box 1.3)
  - 1981/1982-1986/1987 (Box 1.4)
  - 1987/1988-1993/1994 (Box 1.5)
  - 1994/1995-1997/1998 (Box 1.6)
  - 1998/1999-2001/2002 (Box 1.7)
  - 2002/2003-2005/2006 (Box 1.8)
  - 2006/2007-2008/2009 (Box 1.9)
  - 1930-1964 (not inclusive) (Box 2.1)
  - 1966-1971/1972 (Box 2.2)
  - 1972-1978/1979 (Box 2.3)
  - 1979-1983/1984 (Box 2.4)
  - 1984-1988/1989 (Box 2.5)
  - 1989-1992/1993 (Box 2.6)
  - 1993-1996/1997 (Box 2.7)
  - 1997-2000/2001 (Box 2.8)
  - 2001-2004/2005 (Box 2.9)
  - 2005/2006-2008/2009 (Box 2.1)